hexatrack.com 2009-12-31

# HexaTrack - Privacy Policy

At HexaTrack.com we take the privacy of your personal information very seriously. Please rest assured that we will not share your information with outside parties without your knowledge. The only exceptions to this rule would involve extraordinary circumstances: abiding to inquiries by law officials, protecting a HexaTrack member's safety, and legal matters involving HexaTrack.com. 

HexaTrack.com does not collect personal information like names or addresses when you simply visit our website. If you choose to provide that information with us it will only be used to fulfill your request for information. 

If you choose to provide us with personal information like filling out a Contact Us form with an e-mail address and zip code and submitting it to us through the website, we use that information to respond to your message and to help us get you the information you have requested. We will never share any of your information unless we have explicit permission from you or are required to do so by law (by direct request of an identified law enforcement agent). We will never sell any of your private information. 

On occasion, customer support requests and responses from our support staff may be posted in our forum to help others with similar questions. If we do so, we will make sure any of your information is kept private or blanked out. We will never post your name, email or URLs publicly without your permission. 

### Protecting your privacy

Protecting our members' privacy is one of our top priorities. Our staff will not access your account's information and data without your permission. All passwords are encrypted. Your sign-in password cannot be retreived by our staff and will need to be reset in case you lose your password. HexaTrack also forces members to use our site via our SSL secured connection for sign in. In the event the user loads a non-secure URL (http://), the browser will be automatically redirected to the corresponding secure URL (https://). 

### Aggregate anonymous data

We do collect some technical information through our web logs when you visit to help improve our site. When you browse without signing in and read pages or download information from our website, our web server automatically gather and store certain technical information about your visit. This information never identifies who you are. The information we collect and store about your visit is listed below:

  * The web page and IP address from which you access our website
  * The type of browser and operating system used to access our site
  * The date and time you access our site
  * The pages you visit
  * If you came in to our website from another website, the address of that website

This information is only used to help us make the site more useful for you and future visitors. With this data we learn about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology our visitors use. We never track or record information about individuals and their visits. All this information is anonymous.

When you visit some websites, their web servers generate pieces of information known as cookies. Some cookies collect personalized information to recognize your computer in the future.

This is a privacy policy for HexaTrack.com. Our homepage on the Web is located at [ http://www.hexatrack.com](http://www.hexatrack.com/). The full text of our privacy policy is available on the Web at [ http://www.hexatrack.com/privacy.php](http://www.hexatrack.com/privacy.php) Users may go to [ http://www.hexatrack.com/contact-us.php](http://www.hexatrack.com/contact-us.php) for information on how to opt-in or opt-out of use of their information. 

We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this policy. You may contact us by mail at the following address: 

    HexaTrack.com
    211 Warren Street
    Box 62
    Newark, NJ 07102
    US

You may contact us by e-mail at [ hexatrack@gmail.com](mailto:hexatrack@gmail.com). 

## Dispute Resolution and Privacy Seals

We have the following privacy seals and/or dispute resolution mechanisms. If you think we have not followed our privacy policy in some way, they can help you resolve your concern. 

  * **Terms of service** : If you have any questions about our terms of service please contact us at http://www.hexatrack.com 

## Additional Information

This policy was revised July 15, 2008 at 15:00:00 PST. 

## Data Collection

P3P policies declare the data they collect in groups (also referred to as "statements"). This policy contains 2 data groups. The data practices of each group will be explained separately. 

* * *

### Group "Basic information"

We collect the following information: 

  * Click-stream data
  * HTTP protocol elements
  * Search terms

This data will be used for the following purposes:

  * Completion and support of the current activity.
  * Web site and system administration.
  * Research and development.

This data will be used by ourselves and our agents. 

The following explanation is provided for why this data is collected:

> Data collected from all Web users: access logs, and search strings (if entered).

* * *

### Group "Cookies"

At the user's option, we will collect the following data: 

  * HTTP cookies

This data will be used for the following purposes:

  * Research and development.
  * One-time tailoring.

This data will be used by ourselves and our agents. 

The following explanation is provided for why this data is collected:

> Cookies are used to track visitors to our site, so we can better understand what portions of our site best serve you.

* * *

## Cookies

Cookies are a technology which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Web site. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. 

Our site makes use of cookies. Cookies are used for the following purposes: 

  * User targeting 
  * Research and development 

* * *

## Compact Policy Summary

The compact policy which corresponds to this policy is: 

        CP="NOI DSP COR LAW CURa ADMa DEVa TAIa OUR BUS IND UNI COM NAV INT"

The following table explains the meaning of each field in the compact policy. 

**Field**|  **Meaning**  
---|---  
`CP=` | This is the compact policy header; it indicates that what follows is a P3P compact policy.  
`NOI` |  No identifiable information is collected, so no access is possible.   
`DSP` |  The policy contains at least one dispute-resolution mechanism.   
`COR` |  Violations of this policy will be corrected.   
`LAW` |  Privacy law specifies penalties for a violation of this policy.   
`CURa` |  The data is used for completion of the current activity.   
`ADMa` |  The data is used for site administration.   
`DEVa` |  The data is used for research and development.   
`TAIa` |  The data is used for tailoring the site.   
`OUR` |  The data is given to ourselves and our agents.   
`BUS` |  Our business practices specify how long the data will be kept.   
`IND` |  The data will be kept indefinitely.   
`UNI` |  Unique identifiers are collected.   
`COM` |  Computer information is collected.   
`NAV` |  Navigation and clickstream data is collected.   
`INT` |  Interactive data is collected.   
  
The compact policy is sent by the Web server along with the cookies it describes. For more information, see the P3P deployment guide at <http://www.w3.org/TR/p3pdeployment>. 

* * *

## Policy Evaluation

Microsoft Internet Explorer 6 will evaluate this policy's compact policy whenever it is used with a cookie. The actions IE will take depend on what privacy level the user has selected in their browser (Low, Medium, Medium High, or High; the default is Medium. In addition, IE will examine whether the cookie's policy is considered satisfactory or unsatisfactory, whether the cookie is a session cookie or a persistent cookie, and whether the cookie is used in a first-party or third-party context. This section will attempt to evaluate this policy's compact policy against Microsoft's stated behavior for IE6. 

**Note:** this evaluation is currently experimental and should not be considered a substitute for testing with a real Web browser. 

**Satisfactory policy** : this compact policy is considered _satisfactory_ according to the rules defined by Internet Explorer 6. IE6 will accept cookies accompanied by this policy under the High, Medium High, Medium, Low, and Accept All Cookies settings.
